bluepages.com 2017-02-27

# Privacy - Trust Blue Review

Last Modified February 2, 2016  
This Privacy Policy discloses our privacy practices and the possible uses of the information that we gather via https://www.trustbluereview.com, our mobile application(s), and via other submissions by you to Christian Blue Network (CBN). By using this site and services, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, including having your personally identifiable information (“Personal Information” as defined below) used in any of the ways described in this Privacy Policy, you may contact us via US Postal mail: Christian Blue Network 521 Byers Rd Ste 102., Miamisburg, OH 45342.

We may update this Privacy Policy from time-to-time in our sole discretion and it is your responsibility to review the Privacy Policy for any changes each time that you use the site and you are bound by such changes. Your use of the site following us posting a new privacy policy on our site signifies that you agree to and accept the Privacy Policy as modified.

This Privacy Policy applies to the entire Christian Blue Network family of products and services, such as our online services, our print publications, and other Christian Blue Network products or services.

Review Process  
It is our policy to appraise all “Reviews” prior to posting. Positive reviews will be posted right away, negative reviews will be posted after response period, advertiser opt out rights, etc. All companies are given the choice to opt in or opt out of the Review process. Some categories are legally prohibited from participating in the Review Process. 

Information Gathered  
Trust Blue Review collects information on our users in various ways, such as, by your voluntary submissions, participation in services provided via the Site and Services, from third parties with your consent, and through cookie and other tracking technology. Trust Blue Review collects the following information:

Personal Information  
“Personal Information” refers to information that tells us specifically who you are, such as your name, phone number, email, postal address, and possibly information relating to certain support or customer service issues. In many cases, we need this information to provide to you many of the services that you may have requested.

Cellular Phone Use  
By providing us with your cellular telephone number to, you expressly consent to, and authorize us or a third party on our behalf to deliver text messages to the number you provide. This consent encompasses all future autodialed or pre¬recorded telemarketing calls and text messages from us or a third party placing these calls on our behalf.  
You may revoke consent to receive text messages at any time by contacting Trust Blue Review, including by texting STOP.

Submission of Reviews and Comments  
We collect information that you voluntarily provide as part of our site, including messages, posts, comments, responses, and reviews you submit through the site and services., (User Generated Content). Trust Blue Review may in our sole discretion share your user generated content with others such as your business reviews. If you do not want certain information shared with others, you should not submit user generated information, or should not submit user generated content that contains information or personal information you do not want shared in this manner. Once you have submitted content, we reserve the right to publish it in any medium to others.

Collective Information  
We may collect general, non-personal, statistical information about the use of the site, such as how many visitors visit a specific page on the site, how long they stay on that page, and which hyperlinks, if any, they click on. This information represents a generic overview of our users, including their collective viewing habits, and allows us and other third parties to modify information, promotions, offers and/or discounts on products and services based on user traffic and behavior. We collect this information through the use of technologies such as ‘cookies’ and web beacons, which are discussed in greater detail below. We collect this information in order to help enhance the site and services to make for a better visitor experience.

Third Party Information  
We may supplement information you provide to us with information from other sources, such as information to validate or update your address, other demographic and lifestyle information. We use this information to help us maintain the accuracy of the information we collect, to enable us to fulfill our products and services, to target our communications so that we can inform you of products, services and offers that may be of interest and for internal business analysis or other business purposes consistent with our mission.

Cookies  
Trust Blue Review may automatically collect non-personally identifiable information and data through the use of cookies. Cookies are small text files a website uses to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user’s ongoing access to the website and facilitate the use of the website. Cookies also allow a website to track usage behavior and compile site usage information that will allow for the improvement of content and target advertising. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may set your browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. You may also get cookies from our advertisers or other third parties with links on the Site as described below. We do not directly control these cookies. The use of advertising cookies sent by third party ad servers is standard in the Internet industry.  
We may use the services of third parties to collect and use anonymous information about your visits to and interactions with our website through the use of technologies such as cookies to personalize advertisements for goods and services. To learn more, or to opt-out of receiving online display advertisements tailored to your interests by our third party partners, visit the Network Advertising Initiative at www.networkadvertising.org/choices.

Other Tracking Technologies  
Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; the MAC address or other technical information from your mobile device; location information through GPS, WiFi, Bluetooth, or similar technologies; and dates and times that our Site and Services are accessed. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web. Web servers, the computers that ‘serve up’ webpages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address. The Site and Services may also use technology called “tracer tags”. These may also be referred to as “Pixels”, “Clear GIFs” or “Web Beacons”. This technology allows us to understand which pages you visit on our Site and other ways you interact with our Site and Services, such as purchases made through the Site and Services. These tracer tags are used to help us to optimize and tailor our Site and Services for you and other users of our Site and Services. We may link the information we record using tracking technologies to Personal Information we collect.

Use of Information  
The information Trust Blue Review collects is used in a variety of ways, including  
• for internal review;  
• to improve the site and services;  
• to optimize third-party offers of products and/or services;  
• to verify the legitimacy of reviews;  
• to notify you about updates to the site and services;  
• to let you know about products, services, and promotions that you may be interested in;  
• to get reviews;  
• to fulfill and provide products and services, including personalized or enhanced services, requested by you;  
• internal business analysis or other business purposes consistent with our mission;  
• to carry out other purposes that are disclosed to you and to which you consent.

Disclosures and Transfers of Information  
We do not disclose Personal Information to third parties, except when one or more of the following conditions is true:  
• We have your permission to make the disclosure;  
• The disclosure is necessary for the purpose for which the personal information was obtained;  
• The disclosure is permitted by relevant law;  
• The Personal Information to be disclosed is otherwise publicly available in accordance with the applicable law;  
• The disclosure is for our own marketing purposes, or, with your authorization, for the marketing purposes of third parties;  
• The disclosure is combined with information collected from other companies and used to improve and personalize services, content, and advertising from us or third parties;  
• The disclosure is in our sole discretion necessary for the establishment or maintenance of legal claims or legal compliance, to satisfy any law, regulation, subpoena or government request, or in connection with litigation;  
• The disclosure is in our sole discretion about users who we believe are engaged in illegal activities or are otherwise in violation of our Christian Blue Network Membership Agreement, even without a subpoena, warrant or court order;  
• The disclosure is to outside businesses to perform certain services for us, such as maintaining our Site and Services, mailing lists, providing marketing assistance, and data analysis (“Administrative Service Providers”), including Administrative Service Providers outside the country or jurisdiction in which you reside.

Accessing Your Information and Opt-in/Opt-out Requests  
To help you review, edit, and control how we use much of the information we collect about you, you can update certain information and unsubscribe from receiving specific types of email messages and telephone texts. You cannot, however, unsubscribe from receiving certain emails, such as account status and billing related emails, unless you close your account and fulfill any existing contractual obligations. You can also ask us whether we are keeping information about you; to provide you with access to any information we have about you; how your information is being used; update, correct, or delete your information, or opt-out of the collection and use of certain information by sending an email info@trustbluereview.com or by writing us at Christian Blue Network 521 Byers Rd Ste 102; Miamisburg, Oh 45342 specifying the nature and scope of your request. If you choose to delete your information or opt-out of the collection and use of your information, you understand that certain services, may no longer be available to you. In your correspondence, please state the details of your request. We may require proof of your identity before we provide you with the requested information. We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data erased, rectified, amended, or completed. Approved requests will be processed within ten (30) days of the date on which we receive the request.

Data Access, Security,  and Integrity  
As we deem appropriate and as required by the applicable law, we use security measures appropriate for the sensitivity of the Personal Information and consistent with industry standards, including physical, organizational and technological protections, such as firewalls, to protect your Personal Information. However, since no security system is impenetrable, we cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. Personal Information may only be accessed by persons within our organization, our third party service providers who require such access to provide you with the services indicated above, or any other party that you have provided us with authorization to share such information with.  
We retain Personal Information that we collect only as long as reasonably necessary to fulfill the purpose for which it was collected or to otherwise meet any legal requirements.  
Your information may be transferred to, and maintained on, computers located outside of your state, province/territory, or country where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those where you live. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, please be aware that we transfer Personal Information to the United States and process and store it there. As a result, this information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, law enforcement officials and national security authorities in the United States according to its laws. Subject to the applicable laws, we will use reasonable efforts to ensure that appropriate protections are in place to maintain protections on the Personal Information. By submitting your Personal Information, you consent to having your personal data transferred to, processed, and stored in the United States.

Third Party Websites and Links  
Please note that you may have cookies placed on your computer by third party websites that refer you to the Site. Although we do not share your Personal Information with these third party websites unless you have authorized us to do so, they may be able to link certain non-personally identifiable information we transfer to them with Personal Information they previously collected from you. Please review the privacy policies of each website you visit to better understand their privacy practices. Trust Blue Review would like to inform you that anytime you click on links (including advertising banners), which take you to third party websites, you will be subject to the third parties’ privacy policies. While we support the protection of our customer’s privacy on the Internet, Trust Blue Review expressly disclaims any and all liability for the actions of third parties, including but without limitation to actions relating to the use and/or disclosure of Personal Information by third parties. Our site and services may contain links to other sites operated by third parties. Trust Blue Review does not control such other sites and is not responsible for their content, their privacy policies, or their use of personal Information. Trust Blue Review’s inclusion of such links does not, by itself, imply any endorsement of the content on such sites or of their owners or operators except as disclosed on the Site and Services. Any information submitted by you directly to these third parties is subject to that third party’s privacy policy.

Children’s Privacy  
Trust Blue Review does not intend the Site and Services to be used by individuals under the age of majority within the jurisdiction within which they reside without the supervision of a parent or guardian of majority age. Trust Blue Review relies upon such parents or guardians to determine if the Site and Services is appropriate for the viewing, access, or participation by such individuals under the age of majority. If an individual under the age of majority uses the Site and Services, such individual may only use the Site and Services under the supervision of a parent or guardian of majority age.  
We do not seek or knowingly collect any Personal Information about children under 13 years of age. If we become aware that we have unknowingly collected Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will make commercially reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database. If you are the parent or guardian of a minor child who has provided us with Personal Information, you may contact us using the information below to request it be deleted.

Governing Law  
This Privacy Policy and the privacy practices of Trust Blue Review will be subject exclusively to the laws in which Trust Blue Review provides its services.

How To Contact us  
All requests, questions, concerns, or complaints about your Personal Information or this Privacy Policy, please contact Darrel Geis by mail or email at the following:

Christian Blue Network  
521 Byers Rd; Ste 102  
Miamisburg, OH 45342  
E-mail: info@trustbluereview.com
